

I am a transitioning grasshopper-into-professional web designer & front-end developer. I'm interested in all kinds of visual communication, but my major focus is on designing web, mobile & tablet interfaces. In addition, I also specialize in SEO and constantly updating Javascript skills for better crawl on rendered content

# Anya PA Nguyen

# Front-end developer / SEO specialist

## **EXPERIENCE**

2017 - present Web Development and Design Freelancer

Website creation. Wireframe & Mock ups. Prototyping. Design (business card, social media posts, brochure, etc)

2016 - 2017

### **Harvard Innovation Lab (HIL)**

SEO/Socila Media Manager
Provided analytical reports for two start ups at HIL
Managed website and blogging content
Managed interns for social media posts
Optimized website using SEO/SEM tools (HubSpot)
Created paid Facebook campaigns for target markets

2015 (6 months)

#### **Massachusetts Medical Society**

Corporate Marketing Intern
Managed social media activities of the journal
Created monthly social media reports
Learnt posts popularity time and content
through Social Media analytical tools

EDUCATION

2017 - present

2011 - 2015

2011

2010

**UCLA Extension** 

Application Programming

**Northeastern University** 

Business Administraion - Marketing and Finance

Anglo-American School of Moscow International Baccalaureate Diploma

**British Internation School of Moscow** 

International Baccalaureate Diploma

SKILLSETS

Front-end development

HTML/CSS/Bootstrap, Javascript/JQuery, Git/GitHub & Visual Studio SEO/ Marketing

Google Console, Analytics & AdWord, Moz, SEMrush

Design

Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch(Mac), Fresh Paint(Windows)

LINK TO MY WORK

http://anya.pappricot.com/

LINKEDIN